<metadata>
  <title><![CDATA[ HEKTAR BUNDLE ]]></title>
  <threadUrl><![CDATA[https://ftlmultiverse.boards.net/thread/62/mv-5-4-hektar-collection]]></threadUrl>
  <author><![CDATA[ Pepson, DZenith, Chrono Vortex, RoadTrain, Duodecimus ]]></author>
  <version><![CDATA[ 0.1 ]]></version>
  <description>
<![CDATA[ 
An expansion themed after Hektar Industries(tm).
This is a merge of the mods Hektar Collection and Hektar Expansion, and the vast majority of content is sourced from those mods.

Hektar Collection: https://ftlmultiverse.boards.net/thread/62/mv-5-4-hektar-collection
Hektar Expansion: https://ftlmultiverse.boards.net/thread/71/5-4-6-hektar-expansion]

Patch Order:
- Below Multiverse
- There is a minor bug with R&D, and if you use both you should patch Hektar Bundle above R&D


Adds:

- Modular Flak
- Modular Pinpoint
- Modular Bomb
- Modular Mine Launcher

- Modular Laser Drone
- Modular ion Drone
- Modular beam Drone

Each capable of benefiting from Hektar Modules.

Also adds a new cruiser and its 3 variants, all those variants contain their own Modular Artillery, with:

- Modular Beam Artillery
- Modular Missile Artillery
- Modular Laser Artillery

All of those are capable of benefiting from Hektar Modules, their effectiveness is greatly improved from base weapon.

And also adds three new modules, applicable to most existing weapons

- Adaptive Module
- Chain Module
- Charge Module

Credits:

- DZenith: Modular Drone base Art, redraws of modular pinpoint and modular flak
- Chrono Vortex: Code Recommendations, Starmap icon
- Pepson: Code, Art, Design
- RoadTrain: Space Optimization, xml tweaks, Adaptive, Chain and Charge modules, revamp of the storage menu, 
- Duodecimus: Merged HC and HE, and some bug fixing

Changelog, Post merge
- Version 0.1
    merged Hektar Collections and Hektar Expansions into one zip
    fixed hektar player ship achievments
    changed Hektar Manager's bribe ability to not effect drones
    lowered Hektar Manager's damage/repair aura to 1.25
    fixed animations for charge/chain/adaptive modular weapons
    set Missile, Ion and Bomb hektar charge weapons to be magnifiers, gaining 1 damage per charge
    added a number of Hektar weapons to bluelists
]]>
  </description>
</metadata>